GASPARD CHAVARDES

CREATIVE DEVELOPER



(+33) 6 67 37 27 19



chavardes.gaspard@gmail.com



gaspardchavardes.fr

About Me

I'm a 6 years experienced french creative developer who loves to solve problems to reach the best design possible. I built my experience working for several big agencies in France and Europe. I'm currently looking for a permanent job in an agency or freelance missions to build complex designs and fine tuned animations. Please visit my portfolio to see my recent projects.

Experiences

Unseen Studio (former Green Chameleon) 2022 - 2023

Freelance Creative Developper

I had the chance to work for a year as a creative developer for Unseen Studio. I perfected my skills working on complex 3D environments and learned the pipeline needed to achieve theses scenes. Working remotely during this experience also showed I had the rigor to handle big scale projects with coworkers all around Europe.

Hands Agency 2018 - 2022

Lead Front End Developer

Working as a lead front end developer for Hands Agency gave me the opportunity to work for world scale brands in the culture field (Le Palais de Tokyo, Jeu de Paume museum) as well as fashion field (Eric Bompard, Longchamp, Panafrica). I also used this opportunity to self learn WebGL to be able to create original UI animations that integrate inside corporate websites.

Internships and Sandwich courses 2015 - 2018

Studying at Hetic gave me the opportunity to work for great agencies such as (chronologically): This Page Amsterdam, Hello Monday and 84 Paris which taught me how to work collectively with all the professions present inside an agency and the clients.

Education

2018 HETIC Hetic is a multidisciplinary school which provide teaching in Web development, design, and project management

2013 Sciences preparatory class

Language

Français Native
Anglais Fluent

Italien Notions

Expertise

Design

- Adobe Suite
- Figma
- Blender

Technical

- HTML/CSS
- Vue.js/Nuxt.js
- Javascript
- Git
- WebGL/GLSL
- NPM